internetsupervision.com 2011-12-31

# InternetSupervision.com - Privacy Policy

_Please read the following very carefully._  

InternetSupervision.com _(_ hereinafter “ _INTSUP_ ”) values the privacy of our visitors/customers and takes every known precaution to safe guard the information we collect from unauthorized use.  The following is a detailed explanation of the privacy policy for “ _INTSUP_ ”.  Please note that this policy does not apply to those third-party sites that you may visit by selecting a hypertext link on one of our pages.  You will need to consult those web sites’ privacy policies in order to determine how your privacy is protected.   

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

_INTSUP_ believes it is important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site or sign up for one of our related services.  We gather information about you when you visit our pages or the pages of certain _INTSUP_ partners and when you register for any of our services.  We automatically record the name of the domain (for example,"abccompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you are connecting from a university's domain); the IP address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the Internet) from which you access our website; the type of browser and operating system used to access our site; the date and time you access our site; the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site; and the pages you visit.  Additionally, we collect information in the form of a cookie. 

A cookie is a text file that is placed on your computer by a Web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.  Our cookies record your personal preferences that you have submitted to our site at an earlier time.  When you register for any of our services we ask you for your email address, name, phone number, address and city, state and country locations.  Each time you sign into _INTSUP_ after registering for a particular service, you will no longer be an anonymous visitor. 

  **WHY DO WE COLLECT THIS INFORMATION?**

** ** We use this information in order to serve the needs of our customers.  We use the information we collect to personalize the advertising and content you see on our pages.  We also use your information to process your requests to improve our customer service, to contact you, to conduct internal investigations, and to supply anonymous statistics for internal and external clients.  One of the primary functions of using cookies is to save you time when visiting our site. For example, if you customize _INTSUP_ ‘s pages, or register for any of our services, a cookie enables us to summon up your specific information on subsequent visits.  When you return to our web site, the information you previously submitted can be recalled, so you can more conveniently use the features/services you customized. 

**  HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION PROTECTED?**

We use the latest in encryption technology, including 128 bit SSL encryption to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception.  We employ the latest in firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our information storage areas.  We maintain a rigorous hiring process to screen out potential employees with criminal backgrounds.  All employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access, to other individuals or entities.  We also have back up servers and power supplies to guard against power outages and other natural occurrences that could pose a threat to the integrity of your personal information.  Passwords are required in order for you to gain access to your account.  When an employee is terminated or is no longer with the company, we change the access codes that the employee used to access any customer accounts. 

**WHO HAS ACCESS TO MY INFORMATION?**

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except under the following circumstances:

Employees in our technical department may have access to your information in order to conduct routine checks on the integrity of our system and in order to perform necessary maintenance work.  Customer service representatives may also have access to your information in order to better serve you.   

Furthermore, judicial requests by a duly authorized court will require us to divulge certain information regarding you should that situation arise.  We may also share your information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  Finally, should our company ever be bought or sold, your account information would then become the property of the new owner/entity. 

 We may share the statistical information we gather from our web site visitors, such as how many unique IP addresses visit our site, with advertising partners or other third parties. 

**  CAN I CORRECT OR REMOVE INFORMATION FROM YOUR SITE?**

You always have the option to make sure the information we have collected from you is indeed correct.  You also have the option of removing any information from our database that you wish to keep private.  However, please note that removing certain information such as your email address, contact information, and the like may greatly hinder our ability to effectively provide the service you have requested.  We recommend, that you contact us first to discuss which information you may remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you. 

**CAN I OPT OUT OF HAVING CERTAIN INFORMATION COLLECTED?**

You have the option of disabling your computer’s ability to accept or transmit cookies.  This will prevent us from gathering certain non-personally identifiable information from you.  You also have the option of removing yourself from any email distribution list that you may have signed up for.  You also have the option of requesting not to be notified by email of any new product or service we are offering. Please contact us at **info at internetsupervision.com** in order to complete one of the opt-out choices above. 

**NOTICE OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

** ** We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.  However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented.  We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes.  Should the company be bought or sold to someone else, we will take reasonable steps to notify you personally.  You will then be given the option to keep your account open or to terminate.  Please feel free to contact us if you should have any questions regarding this policy or to report a misuse of your personal information. Our Chief Privacy Officer is Patrick Devereaux, and he can be reached at **pjd at emergency24.com**.
